çeviri:T.K
Some keep a diary...
কিছু একটি ডায়েরি রাখুন
Certains tiennent un journal
कुछ एक डायरी रखते हैं
Некоторые ведут дневник ...
Algunas llevan un diario ...
Bəziləri gündəlik tutur...
Bazıları günlük tutuyor.
البعض يحتفظ بمذكرات
Hayal gibi gözüküyor.
Xəyal kimi görünür.
Seems like a fantasy
একটি কল্পনার মত মনে হয়
एक कल्पना की तरह लगता है
Похоже на фантазию
On dirait un fantasme
Pretendiendo que tienen una fantasía
يبدو وكأنه خيال
Amma biraz sevgi və arzu tələb edə bilər Məni qurtaran şey budur
But it may require
তবে এটির প্রয়োজন হতে পারে
हालाँकि, इसकी आवश्यकता हो सकती है
Но это может потребовать
لكنها قد تتطلب
Pero puede requerir
Ama biraz sevgi ve arzu gerektirebilir Beni kurtaran şey bu
Mais cela peut exiger
Un poco de amor deseando que me cubra
Some love and desire its something to cover me
এটি আমাকে আবৃত করার কিছু কিছু ভালবাসা এবং আকাঙ্ক্ষা
यह मुझे कवर करने के लिए कुछ प्यार और इच्छा है
Некоторая любовь и желание это что-то, чтобы покрыть меня
بعض الحب والرغبة في شيء يغطيني (يدفئني) ♪
Un peu d'amour et de désir c'est quelque chose pour me couvrir
Theres never a guarantee
সেখানে কোনও গ্যারান্টি নেই
कोई गारंटी नहीं है
Theres никогда не гарантия
Asla garantisi yok.
Nunca hay garantía
لا يوجد ضمان
Il n'y a jamais de garantie
Əsla zəmanəti yoxdur
That loving is so easy
যে ভালবাসা এত সহজ
Cet amour est si facile
यह प्यार इतना आसान है
Это любить так легко
Öyle sevmek çok kolay.
Belə sevmək çox asandır
Que amar es tan fácil...
هذا الحب سهل جدا
قد يعرّفها البعض على أنها سكر وبراونيز ولكنها حامضة مثل الجير ( تعبير )
Bəziləri onu şəkər və brownilər kimi tanımlaya bilər Amma limon qədər turşdur
Algunos pueden definirlo como azúcar y bizcocho, pero puede ser tan amargo como la lima....
Some may define it as sugar and brownies but sour just as lime is
কেউ কেউ এটিকে চিনি এবং ব্রাউন হিসাবে সংজ্ঞায়িত করতে পারে তবে এটি চুন যেমন হয় তেমন টক হয়
Certains peuvent le définir comme du sucre et des brownies, mais aigre tout comme le citron vert
कुछ इसे चीनी और भूरे रंग के रूप में परिभाषित कर सकते हैं लेकिन यह चूने के समान खट्टा है
Некоторые могут определить это как сахар и пирожные, но кислые, как известь
Bazıları onu şeker ve browniler olarak tanımlayabilir Ama limon kadar ekşi
Uhhh na na na
Uhh na na na
اووو نا نا نا
Uhhh na na na
ওওঔহ না না না
ऊह नो नो नो
Уххх на на на
Uhh na na na uhh na na na na
اووو نا نا نا نا نا
ওওঔহ না না না ওওঔহ না না না
Euh na na na uhh na na na na
ऊँ नहीं नहीं ऊँ नहीं नहीं नहीं
Ухх на нах Ухх на на на на
Uhh na na na uhh na na na na
Uhh na na na na na na
Uhh na na na uhh na na na na na
نا نا نا نا نا نا
ওওঔহ না না না ওওঔহ না না না
Uhh na na na uhh na na na na na
ऊह नो नो ऊओह नो नो नो
Э-э-э-э-э-э-э-э ...
Na na na
না না না
नहीं नहीं नहीं
На на на
Na na na
نا نا نا
না না না
नहीं नहीं नहीं
На на на
Uhh na na na
Uhhhh na na
اوووو نا نا
ওওঔহ না না
ऊओह नहीं नहीं
Ухххх на на
Uhh na na na na na na
Uhhh na na
اوووو نا نا
ওওঔহ না না
ऊओह नहीं नहीं
Уххх на на
Na na na
نا نا نا
না না না
नहीं नहीं नहीं
На на на
نا نا نا
Na na na
না না না
नहीं नहीं नहीं
На на на
Na na na
Uhhh na na
ওওঔহ না না
ऊओह नहीं नहीं
Уххх на на
اوووو نا نا
Uhh na na na
Uhhh na na
Uhhh na na na na
اوووو نا نا نا
Uhh na na na
Uhhh na na na na
ওওঔহ না না না না
ऊह नो नो नो नो
Уххх на на на на
Uhh na na na
اووو نا نا نا
uhhh na na na
ওওঔহ না না না
ऊह नो नो नो
уххх на на на
uhhh na na na
Uhh na na na
uhhh na na
اووو نا نا
ওওঔহ না না
ऊओह नहीं नहीं
ээээ на на
uhhh na na
Une partie de la brise de l'océan
Bəzi okean meh
بعض نسيم المحيط ♪
Viendo las brisas de mar...tu...
Some of the ocean breeze
কিছুটা সমুদ্রের বাতাস
कुछ समुद्री हवा
Немного океанского бриза
Okyanus esintisinin oğlu (Some değil son)
somewhere you promised me
في مكان ما وعدتني ♪
কোথাও তুমি আমাকে প্রতিশ্রুতি দিয়েছিলে
quelque part tu m'as promis
कहीं तुमने मुझसे वादा किया था
где-то ты мне обещал
en algún lugar me prometiste
Bir yerlerde söz verdin bana
Haradasa mənə söz verdin
Atəş kimi bir sevgi, qorxu yox, inkar yox
A love like a fire, no fears, no denial
حب مثل النار ، لا مخاوف ، لا إنكار ♪
একটি ভালোবাসা একটি আগুন, নেই কোন ভয়, নেই কোন অস্বীকার এর মত
Un amour comme un feu, pas de peurs, pas de déni
प्यार एक आग की तरह है, कोई डर नहीं, कोई इंकार नहीं
Любовь, как огонь, нет страхов, нет отрицания
Un amor como el fuego, sin miedos, sin negación...
Ateş gibi bir aşk, korku yok, inkar yok
Sadece beni memnun eden bir şey Elektriği hissediyorum
مجرد شيء يسعدني أشعر بالتيار كهربائي
Juste quelque chose pour me réjouir, je sens l'électricité
Just something to gladden me I feel the electricity
আমাকে সন্তুষ্ট করার মতো কিছু যা আমি বিদ্যুৎ অনুভব করি
मुझे संतुष्ट करने के लिए कुछ है कि मैं बिजली महसूस करता हूं
Просто что-то радовать меня, я чувствую электричество
Algo que me alegra de ti es sentir tu electricidad
Sadəcə məni sevindirəcək bir şey, elektriki hiss edirəm
الإضاءة الخاصة بك ترشدني
Sənin işığın mənə yol göstərir
ton éclairage me guide
tu iluminación me está guiando
your lighting is guiding me
তোমার বিদ্যুৎ আমাকে পরিচালিত করছে
आपकी बिजली मुझे चला रही है
твое освещение ведет меня
Işığın bana yol gösteriyor
Qorxuram, sevirəm bunu gizlədə biləcəyimiz yer yoxdur
أخشى ألا يعجبني أي مكان يمكننا إخفائه
I fear that I like it no place we can hide it
আমি আশঙ্কা করি যে এটি আমার পছন্দ করার মতো কোনও জায়গা যা আমরা আড়াল করতে পারি না
J'ai peur que je l'aime pas d'endroit où nous pouvons le cacher
मुझे यह डर है कि मैं ऐसा स्थान पसंद करता हूं जिसे हम छिपा नहीं सकते
Я боюсь, что мне это не нравится, мы не можем это скрыть
Bunun hoşuma gitmesinden korkuyorum Bunu saklayabileceğimiz bir yer yok
Temo que me guste ningún lugar donde podamos escondernos
Porque es tan dificil encontrarlo uhh na na uhh na na
so hard not to find it uhh na na uhh na na
من الصعب جدًا ألا أجده♪
Tapmamaq çox çətindir
তাই এটা খুঁজে পেতে কঠিন না ওওঔ না না ওওঔ না না
si difficile de ne pas le trouver uhh na na uhh na na
इसलिए इसे खोजना मुश्किल नहीं है
так трудно не найти это э-э-э-э-э-э
Bulmamak çok zor uhh na na uhh na na
Uhh na na na
اوو نا نا اوو نا نا
Uhh na na na na na na na na
na na na euhh na na na
Uhhh na na na uhh na na na
na na na uhh na na na
না না না ওওঔ না না না
नहीं नहीं नहीं नहीं नहीं नहीं
на на на ухх на на на
نا نا نا نا نا نا نا نا نا
na na na na na na na na na
না না না না না না না না না
na na na na na na na na na na
नहीं नहीं नहीं नहीं नहीं नहीं नहीं
на на на на на на на на на
na na na na na na na na na
نا نا نا نا نا نا
Na na na
اوو نا نا نا او نا نا
uhh na na na uh na na
ওওঔ না না না ওওঔ না না
uhh na na na euh na na
ऊँ नहीं नहीं ऊँ नहीं नहीं
э-э-э-э-э-э-э ...
uhh na na na uh na na
Uhh na na na
Uhh na na na na na na
uhh na na na na na
ওওঔ না না না না না
ऊह नहीं नहीं नहीं
эээ на на на на на
uhh na na na na na
نا نا نا نا نا
Na na na
نا نا نا
na na na
না না না
नहीं नहीं नहीं
на на на
na na na
uhh na na
ওওঔ না না
ऊओह नहीं नहीं
эээ на на
uhh na na
اوو نا نا
Uhh na na na na na na
uhh na na
ওওঔ না না
ऊओह नहीं नहीं
эээ на на
uhh na na
(موسيقى)
Uhh na na na
اوو نا نا
uhh na na
ওওঔ না না
ऊओह नहीं नहीं
эээ на на
uhh na na
اوو نا نا نا
uhh na na na
ওওঔ না না না
ऊह नो नो नो
эээ на на на
uhh na na na
Uhh na na na na na na
السبب الذي يجعلنا لا نتخلى عن حبنا بسيط
Basit aşkımızdan vazgeçmememizin sebebi ortada
Sevgimizdən imtina etməyimizin səbəbi sadədir
La razón por la que no renunciamos a nuestro amor es simple
The reason why we don't give up on our love is simple
কেন আমরা আমাদের প্রেমকে ত্যাগ করি না তা সহজ
La raison pour laquelle nous n'abandonnons pas notre amour est simple
हम अपने प्यार का त्याग क्यों नहीं करते इसका कारण सरल है
Причина, по которой мы не сдаемся, проста
We're like the sun and moon
আমরা সূর্য ও চন্দ্রের মত..
Nous sommes comme le soleil et la lune
हम सूर्य और चंद्रमा के समान हैं।
Мы как солнце и луна
Nosotras somos como el sol y la luna
Biz güneş ve ay gibiyiz
نحن مثل الشمس والقمر
Günəş və ay kimiyik
We like to see each other
نحب أن نرى بعضنا البعض
Bir-birimizi görməyi sevirik
আমরা একে অপরকে দেখতে ভালোবাসি
Nous aimons nous voir
हम एक दूसरे को देखना पसंद करते हैं
Нам нравится видеть друг друга
Nos gusta vernos
Birbirimizi parlarken görmeyi seviyoruz, bu gece ve yarın
Shinning bright we have tonight, tomorrow
سطوعنا مشرق الليلة وغدا
Parlayıb yanırıq bizim bu gecəmiz var, sabah
আমাদের আজকের রাত, আগামীকাল জ্বলজ্বলে উজ্জ্বল
Brillant brillant que nous avons ce soir, demain
उज्ज्वल चमकते हुए, हमारे पास आज रात है, कल
Ярко сияем мы сегодня вечером, завтра
Brillar toda la noche y cada mañana
Və digər günlərdə də biz cəhd etməliyik
والأيام الأخرى علينا المحاولة
and the other days that follow we have to try
এবং অন্যান্য দিনগুলি অনুসরণ করে আমাদের চেষ্টা করতে হবে
et les autres jours qui suivent nous devons essayer
और अन्य दिनों के बाद, हमें कोशिश करनी होगी
и в последующие дни мы должны попробовать
y los otros días que siguen tenemos que intentar
Ve onu takip eden diğer günlerde de öyleydi Bazı şeyleri yoluna koymayı denemek zorundayız
لجعل الأمور بخير ، سأغني لك مثل
Ki, hər şey yoluna düşsün
para hacer las cosas bien te cantaré como
to make things right ill sing to you like
সবকিছু ঠিক করতে আমি তোমাকে গান শুনাব
pour que les choses changent mal pour toi
चीजों को सही बनाने के लिए, मैं आपको पसंद करूँगा
чтобы сделать все правильно, плохо петь тебе нравится
Sənə oxuyacağam uhhhh na na na
Sevdiğin şekilde şarkı söyleyeceğim sana
اوووو
uhhhh
ওওঔ
euhhhh
ओह
Uhhhh
uhhhh
na na uhhhh na na na na na
না না ওওঔ না না না না না
नहीं नहीं नहीं नहीं नहीं नहीं
на на ухххх на на на на на
na na uhhhh na na na na na
نا نا اوووو نا نا نا نا
Uhhhh na na na na na
uhhhh na na na na na
ওওঔ না না না না না
ऊह नहीं नहीं नहीं
ухххх на на на на на
uhhhh na na na na na
نا نا نا نا
na na na
না না না
नहीं नहीं नहीं
на на на
na na na
نا نا نا
Na na na
اووو نا نا
uhhh na na
ওওঔ না না
ऊओह नहीं नहीं
ээээ на на
uhhh na na
Uhh na na na
na na na uhhh
না না না ওওঔ
na na na euhhh
नहीं नहीं नहीं
на на на ухххх
na na na uhhh
نا نا ناا نا نا نا
Uhh na na na na na na
na na naa na na na
না না না না না না
नहीं नहीं नहीं नहीं नहीं
на на наа на на на
na na naa na na na
Na na na
na na na na
না না না না
नहीं नहीं नहीं नहीं
на на на на
na na na na
نا نا نا نا
Uhh na na na
اوو نا نا نا
Ooh uh uh na na na
ওওঔ না না না
ऊह नो नो नो
О, э, э, э, на, на, на, на.
Ooh uh uh na na na
Uhh na na na
اوو نا نا نا
Ooh na na na
ওওঔ না না না
ऊह नो नो नो
Оо на на на
Ooh na na na
اووو نا نا نا
Uhh na na na
oooh na na na
ооо на на на на
ওওঔ না না না
ऊह नो नो नो
Nah!
nah!
Неа!
নাহ
नाह
Huuuh!
huuuh!
হহাহ
hahaha
huuuh!
Huuuh!
Huh! səbəb
السبب
eh! la razón
huh! the reason
হাহ! এ কারণ
hein! la raison
हुह! होने के कारण
да! причина
huh!
السبب ...
Səbəb
la razón
Neden?
the reason
এ কারণ
la raison
होने के कारण
причина
la razón por la cual.....
the reason why
السبب لما ♪
Səbəbi isə
কেনো এ কারণ
la raison pour laquelle
कारण क्यों
причина по которой
(Algunas frases fueron modificadas) subtitulos: E.N.A.C
THRACE MUSİC
থ্রেস মিউজিক..
Çeviren ; T.K
Translated by Zakariya Abbas